what's up everybody
this is kathleen anne and welcome to the
hogia channel
[Music]
hello everyone i am back with another
video once again this is kathleen ant
from idol philippines and dagnant
and for today i will be showing you guys
one of who get shop's
products it's actually my first time to
see this product i haven't opened it
since i got here and
let's find out i'm gonna open this
with my scissors i just like to share
before i open this product
that right now i'm wearing a champion
shirt from hooven's shop as well
and
i got this because i was one of the top
three earners
from who beat agency's ticktock
livestreamers
thank you so much
all right
let's
get into it
bubble wrap
[Music]
all right
okay
this is i2 i hope you're pronouncing it
right i2 rgb dash 2 6. all right let's
open it
like pizza oh
oh this is what's inside
so this is a ring light we have this
thing
from here i don't know what you call
this
and this thing this is the thing that
holds your phone i'm sure
wow be careful
why does that sound like
it's breaking
but it's really not breaking
don't worry about me guys it's not
breaking it's not
breaking all right you can bend it right
[Music]
of course our live streamers would know
what this is but of course to those who
are
interested on becoming content creators
or live streamers
you should definitely get one definitely
get ring light and this is the
main thing
so now i'm going to assemble it
um
put this thing here
right there
so far i've only owned two ring lights
touring lights ever in my whole life
streaming career and i've been a live
streamer for like
less than two years less than two
minutes not yet not a few years oh my
gosh
wow
i'm going to put this right here just
connect it
in this motion circular motion
and make sure it
it's intact so i just recognize that
this is the thing that you
connect into the ring light if you're
going to connect it to
a tripod so just basically put it here
here right here
and just twirl it
twirl it rather so this helps
uh the ring light to be stabilized onto
the tripod the cell phone holder is
already attached so basically for you to
be able to put your phone like this
on the self on the cell phone clamp
as you just have to stretch this out
all right so uh for you to be able to
turn on the light the ring light is
connected to
this thing
so
this is the controller and this is the
end of the cord which is a usb port
where you're going to connect it to uh
an adapter an adapter all right so this
is the controller for the
ring light
and now i am going to connect
the usb port into an adapter
so that that's it
look at that it's very bright i'm using
a very small ring light right now
it's like a desk
ring light but this is like another
level
when you put it there it actually
actually looks good i'm going to use
this controller
and go up
you see the controller has
this option so you have up down
on and off on or off rather rgb
and mode
so i'm gonna press up and let's see
what's gonna happen
getting a lot brighter and when we press
down
it's going
shades
darker darker all right so that's like
six right six so one two three four five
six
oh eight seven
eight oh it's eight
what
[Music]
that's not
is it more than eight let me check
okay this is the top right this is the
all right one two three four five
six seven
eight
nine nine
ten eleven
11 oh my gosh it has 11 options
mine has like
i don't know three
now let's press on
rgb
let's see let's see
oh that's red i'm not sure if you can
see that it's red but it's actually red
with the colors you don't really have
much choice
it doesn't change like
the brightness doesn't change the
brightness level
let's press the rgb again and now it's
green kind of like
a circular lightsaber
okay moving on let's press rgb again
now it's blue
and there is light green
i'm not sure if you could see it clearly
but if i put it through my
can you see it it's light green
it's purple oh my gosh i love purple
purple
and it's light blue
and it's hand again oh
it's changing
it's hanging
easy
oh it's a green
from orange and now it's it's blue from
orange blue and green and then blue
let's see if it's still gonna change
next
it's different colors
it has like these different colors and
it's kind of changing as well next is
blue and red look it's circling it's
circling
now it's red and blue i it's green and
blue rather
lots of
color changes you can have a lot of fun
oh
[Music]
hey
i'm dancing to nothing anyway
let me change it again
[Music]
now it's back to red
and at the end of it there's a lot of
uh choices
play around with this ring light just
have to keep on pressing the rgb button
but there's one more button that we
haven't pressed which is mode so i'm
going to click that and we will see
this is a dim yellow
yellow
all right it can go
11. levels brighter yo that is crazy
11 levels it's like a lot
you can control the light that you need
for your
videos or photos photo shoots content
whatever it is
this is just crazy there's a lot of
choices here
and this is bright white this is like
like the brightest white
i don't know how to explain that
so it can go
levels lower
lower common lower so it has three modes
the bright white one
the yellowish white
and the yellow
this is like perfect for like mellow
themed photo shoots or content right
this is the lighting this is the light
wow
so that is our product for today if you
guys are interested to find
this ring light just
search up copy and shop on shopee
s-h-o-p-e-e dot p-h and you can find it
there just search up who band shop and
also you could search the website itself
who been shop dot ph you guys could also
find this shirt on who being shop if you
want to get one it's very comfortable as
well
and very fashionable please also use my
voucher code if you want to get a
discount please make sure to check it
out you can use my voucher code on
shopping and if you want to be updated
with whovian shops products make sure to
follow them on facebook and instagram
phobia and shop thank you so much guys
please subscribe to whovian channel if
you reach the end of this video give
this video a like share this to your
friends and if you want to connect with
me this is kathleen and just make sure
to follow me on my instagram and tech
talk i'm kathleen and i am
k-a-t-h-l-e-e-n-a-n-n-e
and on my facebook page please like it
kathleen space app
thank you so much for watching bye
[Music]